sidroth.org 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Sid Roth – It’s Supernatural! | sidroth.org

Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site located at the URL www.sidroth.org.

In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use. Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our Site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.

1\. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of;  
2\. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the Site;  
3\. Who collects such information;  
4\. How such information is used;  
5\. With whom your information may be shared;  
6\. What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information;  
7\. What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control;  
8\. and, How you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.

**Use of “Cookies” (“Remember Me”)** :  
Our site uses cookies to identify end users based on their visit to our websites and/or other sites on the Internet. We also use cookies to analyze website traffic and performance. Cookies are pieces of information that some Web sites transfer to the computer that is browsing that Web site and are used for record-keeping purposes at many Web sites. Use of cookies makes Web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular Web site and to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision by sending an email to [info@SidRoth.org](mailto:info@SidRoth.org "E-mail info@SidRoth.org"). Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.

**What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information** :  
Our registration forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, format preference (HTML vs. Text), address, interests, and similar information. We do not request or store sensitive information from our visitors, such as credit card or social security numbers. Our site collect/collects data related to targeted advertising and the behavior demonstrated by end users on advertiser websites. Data is converted into obfuscated audience lists from which individual identities cannot be determined by Third-Party vendors. Specifically, collected data is cookie data which our/the DSP platforms process, creating audiences and attributing actions to specific ad campaigns. Data is stored in vetted third-party platforms which facilitate the collection of this data through secured tags. These platforms all conform to necessary data privacy laws, and allow for the exercising of all rights of data subjects. Lastly, platforms that allow for user-level tracking do so only through data gathered with proper consent, and obscure any form of user identification.

**Internet Protocol Address** :  
We collect an IP address from all visitors to our Site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site, and deliver customized, personalized content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them.

**Security** :  
All information provided to Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our Site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.

**Tell-A-Friend** :  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our Site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the Site. Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

**Other Web Sites** :  
Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site for which Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.

**Social Media**  
a) Facebook – Sid Roth’s It’s Supernatural manages a publicly accessible Facebook page.  This page must be “Liked” by individuals through their own Facebook profiles — employees of It’s Supernatural and Messianic Vision will never ask fans and followers of Sid Roth’s It’s Supernatural’s Facebook page to accept them as friends over their personal profiles.  Individuals must “Like” Sid Roth’s It’s Supernatural’s page of their own volition.

b) Twitter – Sid Roth’s It’s Supernatural manages a publicly accessible Twitter page.  This page must be “Followed” by individuals through their own Twitter profiles — employees of It’s Supernatural and Messianic Vision will never ask fans and followers of Sid Roth’s It’s Supernatural’s Twitter page to accept them as friends over their personal profiles. Individuals must “Follow” Sid Roth’s It’s Supernatural’s page of their own volition.

**Contacting the Web Site** :  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact:

Sid Roth’s Messianic Vision  
P.O. Box 39222  
Charlotte, NC 28278

You can also send an email to: [info@sidroth.org](mailto:info@sidroth.org "E-mail info@sidroth.org").
